[
  {
    "question"         : "ア",
    "answer"           : "a",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "イ",
    "answer"           : "i",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ウ",
    "answer"           : "u",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "エ",
    "answer"           : "e",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "オ",
    "answer"           : "o",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "カ",
    "answer"           : "ka",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "キ",
    "answer"           : "ki",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ク",
    "answer"           : "ku",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ケ",
    "answer"           : "ke",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "コ",
    "answer"           : "ko",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "サ",
    "answer"           : "sa",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "シ",
    "answer"           : "shi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ス",
    "answer"           : "su",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "セ",
    "answer"           : "se",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ソ",
    "answer"           : "so",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "タ",
    "answer"           : "ta",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "チ",
    "answer"           : "chi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ツ",
    "answer"           : "tsu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "テ",
    "answer"           : "te",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ト",
    "answer"           : "to",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ナ",
    "answer"           : "na",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ニ",
    "answer"           : "ni",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヌ",
    "answer"           : "nu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ネ",
    "answer"           : "ne",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ノ",
    "answer"           : "no",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ハ",
    "answer"           : "ha",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヒ",
    "answer"           : "hi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "フ",
    "answer"           : "fu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヘ",
    "answer"           : "he",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ホ",
    "answer"           : "ho",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "マ",
    "answer"           : "ma",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ミ",
    "answer"           : "mi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ム",
    "answer"           : "mu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "メ",
    "answer"           : "me",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "モ",
    "answer"           : "mo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヤ",
    "answer"           : "ya",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ユ",
    "answer"           : "yu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヨ",
    "answer"           : "yo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ラ",
    "answer"           : "ra",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "リ",
    "answer"           : "ri",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ル",
    "answer"           : "ru",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "レ",
    "answer"           : "re",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ロ",
    "answer"           : "ro",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ワ",
    "answer"           : "wa",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヲ",
    "answer"           : "wo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ン",
    "answer"           : "n",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ガ",
    "answer"           : "ga",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ギ",
    "answer"           : "gi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "グ",
    "answer"           : "gu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ゲ",
    "answer"           : "ge",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ゴ",
    "answer"           : "go",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ザ",
    "answer"           : "za",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ジ",
    "answer"           : "ji",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ズ",
    "answer"           : "zu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ゼ",
    "answer"           : "ze",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ゾ",
    "answer"           : "zo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ダ",
    "answer"           : "da",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヂ",
    "answer"           : "ji",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヅ",
    "answer"           : "zu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "デ",
    "answer"           : "de",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ド",
    "answer"           : "do",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "バ",
    "answer"           : "ba",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ビ",
    "answer"           : "bi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ブ",
    "answer"           : "bu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ベ",
    "answer"           : "be",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ボ",
    "answer"           : "bo",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "パ",
    "answer"           : "pa",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ピ",
    "answer"           : "pi",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "プ",
    "answer"           : "pu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ペ",
    "answer"           : "pe",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ポ",
    "answer"           : "po",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  },
  {
    "question"         : "ヴ",
    "answer"           : "vu",
    "correctGuesses"   : 0,
    "incorrectGuesses" : 0,
    "ratio"            : 0
  }
]
